Finding Aid for the George Schaefer Papers LSC.0588
UCLA Library Special Collections
George Schaefer papers
1951-1991
UCLA Library Special Collections
Schaefer, George
LSC.0588
46.6 Linear Feet (56 boxes, 23 oversize flat boxes, 1 map folder, and 1 shoe box)
George Schaefer (1920-1991) was a producer and director for television, film, and theatre productions. The collection consists of correspondence, production files, and scrapbooks related to Schaefer's career, particularly his work with television's Hallmark Hall of Fame.
Conditions on Access
Open for research. All requests to access special collections materials must be made in advance using the request button located on this page.
Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
PORTIONS OF THIS COLLECTION HAVE BEEN DIGITIZED. See the Online Items Available note for the link to the digitized materials.
Provenance/Source of Acquisition
Gift of Mildred Schaefer, 1999.
UCLA Catalog Record ID
UCLA Catalog Record ID: 9951631953606533
Biography/History
George Schaefer (1920-1997) earned his B.A. from Lafayette College before attending Yale Drama School for one year. He enlisted in the army during World War II, where he directed over fifty plays for the Central Pacific Base Command. Following the war, he headed to New York to continue his work in the theatre. In 1953 he began his collaboration with Hallmark Hall of Fame television productions, directing a live televised stage performance of Hamlet. Schaefer eventually produced and/or directed 57 Hallmark productions, while he continued his work in theatre, feature films, and other television movies. His career spanned over 60 years, during which time he received many accolades. In 1985, he became the chair of the UCLA School of Theatre, Film, and Television. Two years later, he became Associate Dean. Schaefer died following a long illness in 1991.
Scope and Content
The collection consists of George Schaefer's correspondence and production files related to over eighty television, theatre, and film projects. Files include production materials, clippings, publicity kits, scripts, and business correspondence, including correspondence originating from Compass Productions and Foote, Cone, and Belding. The bulk of material relates to Schaefer's directorial and production responsibilities for approximately 40 Hallmark Hall of Fame television productions. The files also include scrapbooks of publicity materials and clippings, posters, a portion of his many awards and honors, and small amount of teaching material from Schaefer's tenure as Department Chair and Associate Dean of the UCLA School of Theatre, Film and Television.
Organization and Arrangement
Arranged in the following series:
Awards and honors, 1962-1982 (5 boxes).
Feature films, 1951-1981 (5 boxes), subseries A-B as follows:
Production files, 1951-1981.
Scrapbook, 1968-1969.
Hallmark Hall of Fame, 1953-1982 (48 boxes), subseries A-D as follows:
Foote, Cone, and Belding correspondence, 1959-1982.
Hallmark files, 1957-1982.
Production files, 1953-1982.
Scrapbooks, 1959-1969.
Miscellaneous, 1957-1991 (3 boxes), subseries A-C as follows:
Compass Productions, 1957-1973.
Production materials, 1961-1976.
UCLA, 1970-1991.
Television, 1959-1989 (11 boxes), subseries A-B as follows:
Production files, 1959-1989.
Scrapbook, 1966-1968.
Theatre, 1961-1987 (4 boxes), subseries A-B as follows:
Production files, 1961-1987.
Scrapbook, 1961-1963.
Existence and Location of Copies
Portions of this collection have been digitized and are available online: George Schaefer papers (1 item).
Television producers and directors -- United States -- Archives.; Schaefer, George -- Archives; Compass Productions; Hallmark Hall of Fame Productions, Inc.
- Series 1: Awards and honors, 1962-1982; 5 boxes
  Scope and Contents note
  Assorted awards, certificates, and honors for George Schaefer's work in television and film. Arranged alphabetically by the name of the awarding institution.
  - American Women in Film and Television, INC., 1977, 1982.; 2 items. (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Award certificate for A Piano for Mrs. Cimino and Amelia Earhart.
  - Chicago International Film Festival., 1975.; 1 item. (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Award plaque for Sandburg's Lincoln, "The Unwilling Warrior."
  - Director's Guild of America., 1968-1980.; 10 items. (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Award plaques for The Second Barry Manilow Special, First You Cry, and Barry Manilow, One Voice; congratulatory correspondence on winning the Director's Guild of America Award.
  - Fairleigh-Dickinson University., 1969.; 1 item. (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Concilium Musei Novi Eboraci award certificate.
  - Film Advisory Board., 1977 June.; 1 item. (Box 1, Folder 5)
    Award plaque for Our Town.
  - Hallmark Hall of Fame--A Salute to George Schaefer., 1964-1965.; 12 items. (Box 2, Folder 1)
    Assorted printed materials, correspondence, press release, clippings (to celebrate his 50th Hallmark production). See also Box 80 for a sound reel of an interview with George Schaefer and "Wally" at the event.
  - National Academy of Television Arts and Sciences--Anastasia., 1967 March.; 1 item. (Box 2, Folder 2)
    Plaque for Emmy nomination for "Outstanding Directorial Achievement in Drama."
  - National Academy of Television Arts and Sciences--Award certificates., 1972-1979.; 6 items. (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Certificates for nomination for productions including War of Children, Our Town, The Second Barry Manilow Special, Bell System Special, Blind Ambition.
  - National Academy of Television Arts and Sciences--Do Not Go Gentle Into That Good Night., 1967 October.; 2 items. (Box 2, Folder 4)
    Plaques for Emmy nominations for "Outstanding Directorial Achievement in Drama"; "Outstanding Dramatic Program."
  - National Academy of Television Arts and Sciences--Eagle in a Cage., 1965 October.; 2 items. (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - National Academy of Television Arts and Sciences--Elizabeth the Queen., 1968 January.; 1 item. (Box 2, Folder 6)
    Plaque for Emmy nomination for "Outstanding Dramatic Program."
  - National Academy of Television Arts and Sciences--Hallmark Hall of Fame., 1965 January.; 1 item. (Box 3, Folder 1)
    Plaque for excellence for the Hallmark Hall of Fame.
  - National Academy of Television Arts and Sciences--Inherit the Wind., 1965 Novermber.; 2 items. (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - National Academy of Television Arts and Sciences--The Invincible Mr. Disraeli., 1963 April.; 1 item. (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - National Academy of Television Arts and Sciences--The Magnificent Yankee., 1965 January.; 2 items. (Box 3, Folder 4)
    Plaques for Emmy nominations for outstanding individual achievements in entertainment; Outstanding program achievements in entertainment.
  - National Academy of Television Arts and Sciences--The Patriots., 1963 November.; 1 item. (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - National Academy of Television Arts and Sciences--Victoria Regina (folder 1 of 3)., 1962.; 1 item. (Box 4, Folder 1)
    Plaque for Emmy nomination for outstanding program achievement in the field of drama.
  - National Academy of Television Arts and Sciences--Victoria Regina (folder 2 of 3)., 1962.; 1 item. (Box 4, Folder 2)
    Plaque for Emmy nomination for program of the year.
  - National Academy of Television Arts and Sciences--Victoria Regina (folder 3 of 3)., 1962.; 1 item. (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Tribute to George Schaefer--Correspondence., 1967, 1969.; ca. 60 items. (Box 4, Folder 4)
    Presented by the New York Cultural Center in association with Fairleigh Dickinson University: Includes general correspondence related to planning and promotion of the event, Hallmark and property network-union clearance.
  - Tribute to George Schaefer--Photographs., 1969.; 16 items. (Box 4, Folder 5)
    Six 8x10 stills, 10 key sheets (1 in color).
  - Tribute to George Schaefer--Publicity., 1969.; 3 items. (Box 4, Folder 6)
    Assorted print materials, correspondence, clippings.
  - Tribute to George Schaefer--Catalog and program., 1969.; 4 items. (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - TV Guide awards--Arsenic and Old Lace., 1962.; 1 item. (Box 5, Folder 1)
    Nomination award for best single dramatic program.
  - TV Guide awards--Victoria Regina., 1962.; 1 item. (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - TV Guide awards--Pygmalion., 1963.; 1 item. (Box 5, Folder 3)
    Nomination award for best single dramatic musical or variety program.
  - TV Guide awards--Abe Lincoln in Illinois., 1964.; 1 item. (Box 5, Folder 4)
    Nomination award for best single dramatic, musical, or variety program.
- Series 2: Feature films, 1951-1981; 5 boxes
  Production files and a scrapbook related to George Schaefer's work in feature films. Arranged in two subseries:
  2A. Production files, 1951-1981(4 boxes).
  2B. Scrapbook, 1968- 1969 (1 box).
  - Subseries 2A: Production files, 1951-1981
    Arranged alphabetically by production name.
    - An Enemy of the People--Casting., 1974-1977.; ca. 60 items. (Box 6, Folder 1)
      Correspondence, playbill, lists, magazine.
    - An Enemy of the People--Clippings., 1977-1979, 1981.; ca. 50 items. (Box 6, Folder 2)
      Clippings and photocopies of clippings.
    - An Enemy of the People--Correspondence., 1976-1981.; ca. 50 items. (Box 6, Folder 3)
      Regarding reviews, post-production, and legal issues.
    - An Enemy of the People--File copy for George Schaefer., 1976.; 9 items. (Box 6, Folder 4)
      Correspondence, press release, literary purchase agreement.
    - An Enemy of the People--Financial., 1976-1977.; ca. 40 items. (Box 6, Folder 5)
      Balance sheets, estimated costs, expense statements, invoices, correspondence, cast lists, budgets, and miscellaneous printed material.
    - An Enemy of the People--McQueen, Steve., 1976.; 6 items. (Box 6, Folder 6)
      Correspondence and directions.
    - An Enemy of the People--Office supplies., 1976.; 5 items. (Box 6, Folder 7)
      Correspondence, agreements, and assorted printed materials.
    - An Enemy of the People--Production authorizations., 1976.; 2 items. (Box 6, Folder 8)
      Authorizations for engagement of artists and memoranda.
    - An Enemy of the People--Production file., 1976-1977.; 9 items. (Box 6, Folder 9)
      Assorted printed materials, correspondence, cast/production/crew lists, schedules, handwritten notes, and 6 photographs of décor.
    - An Enemy of the People--Production reports and call sheets., 1976.; 2 items. (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - An Enemy of the People--Publicity (folder 1 of 2)., 1976-1978.; 12 items. (Box 7, Folder 2)
      Correspondence, photograph, portfolio featuring Steve McQueen, and assorted printed materials.
    - An Enemy of the People--Publicity (folder 2 of 2)., 1976-1978.; 8 items. (Box 7, Folder 3)
      Copies of The Federalist, Daily Variety, and the Hollywood Reporter; Montreal film festival catalog.
    - An Enemy of the People--Publicity reports., 1977.; 6 items. (Box 7, Folder 4)
      Audience preview reports.
    - An Enemy of the People--Script (folder 1 of 4)., 1976 June.; 2 items. (Box 7, Folder 5)
      First compilation.
    - An Enemy of the People--Script (folder 2 of 4)., 1976 June.; 1 item. (Box 8, Folder 1)
      First draft.
    - An Enemy of the People--Script (folder 3 of 4)., 1976 August.; 4 items. (Box 8, Folder 2)
      First draft with annotations.
    - An Enemy of the People--Script (folder 4 of 4)., 1951, 1975-1976.; 10 items. (Box 8, Folder 3)
      Assorted correspondence, magazines, and printed materials regarding the script; acting edition.
    - An Enemy of the People--Set designs., ca. 1976.; 4 items. (Box 8, Folder 4)
      Oversized plans for the set designs, by MGM studios.
    - Generation--Casting., no date.; ca. 150 items. (Box 8, Folder 5)
      Notecards for the roles of Doris, Desmond, and Hey Hey.
    - Love Letters of a Portugese Nun--Clippings., 1962-1964.; 7 items. (Box 8, Folder 6)
      Clippings regarding speculation on the film, to star Natalie Wood (never made).
    - Old Times--Production file., 976.; ca. 15 items. (Box 8, Folder 7)
      Assorted printed materials from Solar, First Artists, and Warner future productions; photocopy of "The Promise"; clipping; correspondence with Harold Pinter (film never made).
    - Once Upon a Scoundrel--Clippings., 1972-1974.; 16 items. (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Once Upon a Scoundrel--Correspondence., 1971-1980.; ca. 50 items. (Box 8, Folder 9)
      Regarding reviews, post-production, legal and financial issues.
    - Once Upon a Scoundrel--Publicity., 1968-1978.; 15 items. (Box 9, Folder 1)
      Magazines, reviews, and press releases. See also box 79 for a "Scoundrel" cassette. See also box 77 for a 1974 portfolio.
    - Once Upon a Scoundrel--Script (folder 1 of 2)., 1972.; 2 items. (Box 9, Folder 2)
      Two shooting scripts, with annotations.
    - Once Upon a Scoundrel--Script (folder 2 of 2)., 1972.; 1 item. (Box 9, Folder 3)
      Shooting script, labeled "Adie's."
    - Pendulum--Clippings., 1968-1968.; 4 items. (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Pendulum--Key sheets., 1968.; ca. 100 items. (Box 9, Folder 5)
      Black and white photographic key sheets. See also box 77 for 44 oversized sheets.
    - Pendulum--Script (folder 1 of 3)., 1968.; 1 item. (Box 9, Folder 6)
      Final.
    - Pendulum--Script (folder 2 of 3)., 1967-1968.; 1 item. (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Pendulum--Script (folder 3 of 3)., 1967.; 1 item. (Box 9, Folder 8)
      Original.
    - The Slender Thread--Clippings., 1962-1963.; 5 items. (Box 9, Folder 9)
      Clippings regarding speculation on the film (never made).
  - Subseries 2B: Scrapbook, 1968-1969
    - Scrapbook., 1968-1969.; 1 item. (Box 10, Folder 1)
      Clippings and publicity material related to Pendulum, Generation, The Trap, Willy, We Have Always Lived in Castle, Doctor's Wives (Suburbia), and the DGA 1968 awards.
- Series 3: Hallmark Hall of Fame, 1953-1982; 48 boxes
  Business correspondence, production files and scrapbooks related to George Schaefer's work with Hallmark Hall of Fame productions. Arranged in four subseries:
  3A. Foote, Cone and Belding correspondence, 1959-1982 (1.5 boxes).
  3B. Hallmark files, 1957-1982 (1.5 boxes).
  3C. Production files, 1953-1982 (35 boxes).
  IIID. Scrapbooks, 1959-1969 (10 boxes).
  .
  - Subseries 3A: Foote, Cone and Belding correspondence., 1959-1982.
    General business correspondence. Files arranged in original chronological order, by year.
    - Foote, Cone and Belding correspondence. (Box 11, Box 12)
      General correspondence regarding Hallmark Hall of Fame productions, in chronological order by year.
  - Subseries 3B: Hallmark files., 1957-1982.
    Assorted files related to Hallmark productions and the Hallmark Hall of Fame, including correspondence. Arranged alphabetically by subject of the file contents.
    - Below-the-line costs., 13 items. (Box 12, Folder 10)
      Assorted price sheets for Hallmark shows, including Kiss Me Kate, Johnny Belinda, Dial M for Murder, On Borrowed Time, Green Pastures, Twelfth Night, The Christmas Tree, Berkeley Square, The Green Pastures, and Ah, Wilderness.
    - Correspondence--Hallmark (folder 1 of 4)., ca. 50 items. (Box 12, Folder 11)
      General correspondence relating to Hallmark productions.
    - Correspondence--Hallmark (folder 2 of 4)., ca. 25 items. (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence--Hallmark (folder 3 of 4)., ca. 75 items. (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence--Hallmark (folder 4 of 4)., ca. 75 items. (Box 13, Folder 1)
      General correspondence relating to Hallmark productions, several contracts.
    - Television's Golden Crown., ca. 30 items. (Box 13, Folder 10)
      Exhibition catalog, correspondence, invitation list, press releases, and 8 x 10 black and white photographs related to the Hallmark Gallery on 5th Avenue.
    - Correspondence--NBC (folder 1 of 2)., ca. 30 items. (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence--NBC (folder 2 of 2)., ca. 30 items. (Box 13, Folder 3)
      Correspondence and agreements regarding arrangements between Hallmark and NBC.
    - Hall, Joyce C., 6 items. (Box 13, Folder 4)
      Assorted print materials related to a luncheon in honor of Joyce C. Hall. See also box 79 for a sound reel of Hall's Emmy Award acceptance speech.
    - Hall of Fame history., ca. 20 items. (Box 13, Folder 5)
      Assorted printed materials and clippings.
    - Haun, Delcan., 15 items. (Box 13, Folder 6)
      Freelance photographer hired by FCB to work on Hallmark productions. Correspondence.
    - Heck, Homer R., 4 items. (Box 13, Folder 7)
      Speech from a presentation to the American Women in Radio and Television, entitled "The Hallmark Hall of Fame: A Study in Lonliness," and clippings.
    - Public relations documentary., 12 items. (Box 13, Folder 8)
      Correspondence relating to preliminary plans for a promotional film on the making of Hallmark Hall of Fame productions.
    - Talking Books for the Blind., ca. 75 items. (Box 13, Folder 9)
      Correspondence.
  - Subseries 3C: Production files., 1953-1982.
    - Abe Lincoln in Illinois--Clippings., 11 items. (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Abe Lincoln in Illinois--Correspondence., 5 items. (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Abe Lincoln in Illinois--Publicity., 13 items. (Box 14, Folder 3)
      Slide, playbill, portfolio, correspondence, press releases, and assorted printed materials. See also box 78 for 3 LPs.
    - Abe Lincoln in Illinois--Repeat., 7 items. (Box 14, Folder 4)
      Clippings, press releases, and assorted printed materials for rerun (see oversize folder 81 for poster).
    - Abe Lincoln in Illinois--Script., 1 item. (Box 14, Folder 5)
      Revised, as aired.
    - The Admirable Crichton--Clippings., ca. 25 items. (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - The Admirable Crichton--Correspondence., 11 items. (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - The Admirable Crichton--Publicity., ca. 25 items. (Box 14, Folder 8)
      Playbill, press releases, and assorted printed materials.
    - The Admirable Crichton--Script., 1 item. (Box 14, Folder 9)
      Annotated.
    - Anastasia--Correspondence., ca. 50 items. (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Anastasia--Production and format., 16 items. (Box 15, Folder 2)
      Assorted printed materials.
    - Anastasia--Publicity., 10 items. (Box 15, Folder 3)
      Playbill, press releases, clippings, and assorted printed materials (see oversize folder 81 for poster).
    - Arsenic and Old Lace--Key sheets., 18 items. (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Arsenic and Old Lace--Publicity., ca. 20 items. (Box 15, Folder 5)
      Slide, playbill, portfolio, correspondence, press releases, and assorted printed materials.
    - Arsenic and Old Lace--Script., 1 item. (Box 15, Folder 6)
      Revised, as aired, with supporting production materials.
    - Barefoot in Athens--Correspondence., ca. 75 items. (Box 15, Folder 7)
      Fan mail and letters from Foote, Cone & Belding, Hallmark, and Reeves Sound Studios, NBC.
    - Barefoot in Athens--Production and format., 9 items. (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Barefoot in Athens--Publicity., 29 items. (Box 16, Folder 1)
      Playbill, clippings, press releases (see oversize folder 81 for poster).
    - Barefoot in Athens--Script (folder 1 of 2)., 1 item. (Box 16, Folder 2)
      With music cues.
    - Barefoot in Athens--Script (folder 2 of 2)., 1 item. (Box 16, Folder 3)
      Annotated, with supporting production materials.
    - Blithe Spirit--Compass Productions., ca. 50 items. (Box 16, Folder 4)
      Correspondence and signed agreements.
    - Blithe Spirit--Correspondence., ca. 50 items. (Box 16, Folder 5)
      Fan mail and letters from Foote, Cone & Belding, Hallmark, and NBC.
    - Blithe Spirit--Key sheets., 54 items. (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Blithe Spirit--Legal file., ca. 50 items. (Box 17, Folder 1)
      Rights and permissions correspondence, signed agreements.
    - Blithe Spirit--Production and format., 6 items. (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Blithe Spirit--Publicity., 14 items. (Box 17, Folder 3)
      Playbills, press releases, photographs, and clippings. See also box 78 for 3 LPs: 2 of "Trumpet solo" (duplicates?) and 1 of music cues.
    - Blithe Spirit--Script., 1 item. (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Captain Brassbound's Conversion--Correspondence., 47 items. (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Captain Brassbound's Conversion--Publicity., 27 items. (Box 17, Folder 6)
      Clippings, advertisements, press releases, and assorted printed materials. See also box 78 for 2 LPs of Hallmark Playhouse music cues with tracks 1-9 and 10-18A marked "air and protection copy" (duplicates?).
    - Captain Brassbound's Conversion--Script., 1 item. (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - The Cradle Song--Contracts and reports., 19 items. (Box 18, Folder 1)
      Signed contracts and agreements, and correspondence regarding the P& W Remittance Report; AFTRA Production Report.
    - The Cradle Song--Correspondence., ca. 25 items. (Box 18, Folder 2)
      Letters regarding Foote, Cone, and Belding, and legal, billing, and payroll issues.
    - The Cradle Song--Key sheets., 23 items. (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - The Cradle Song--Production and format., 13 items. (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - The Cradle Song--Publicity., 15 items. (Box 18, Folder 5)
      Press releases, portfolio, clippings, and assorted printed materials.
    - The Cradle Song--Script (folder 1 of 2)., 1 item. (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - The Cradle Song--Script (folder 2 of 2)., 1 item. (Box 18, Folder 7)
      Second version, as taped.
    - The Cradle Song--Set design., 16 items. (Box 18, Folder 8)
      Oversized drawings and perspectives.
    - A Cry of Angels--Key sheets., ca. 45 items. (Box 19, Folder 1)
      Proof sheets and negatives.
    - A Cry of Angels--Publicity., 4 items. (Box 19, Folder 2)
      Producer's report, press releases, clippings, and assorted printed materials. See also box 80 for 1 acetate safety reel from Reeves Soundcraft.
    - A Cry of Angels--Script., 11 items. (Box 19, Folder 3)
      Annotated, and with supporting production materials.
    - Cyrano de Bergerac--Correspondence., 46 items. (Box 19, Folder 4)
      Fan mail, and letters from Foote, Cone & Belding, NBC, and Revere High School.
    - Cyrano de Bergerac--Production and format., 13 items. (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Cyrano de Bergerac--Publicity., ca. 30 items. (Box 19, Folder 6)
      Press releases, clippings, portfolio, slide.
    - Cyrano de Bergerac--Script., 1 item. (Box 19, Folder 7)
      Master revised.
    - A Doll's House--Contracts., ca. 20 items. (Box 20, Folder 1)
      Signed agreements/contracts and correspondence.
    - A Doll's House--Correspondence., ca. 25 items. (Box 20, Folder 2)
      Fan mail and letters from George Schaefer Productions.
    - A Doll's House--Key sheets., 17 items. (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - A Doll's House--Production and format., ca. 20 items. (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - A Doll's House--Publicity., 11 items. (Box 20, Folder 5)
      Press releases, clippings, and assorted printed materials.
    - A Doll's House--Script., 1 item. (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Eagle in a Cage--Correspondence., ca. 50 items. (Box 20, Folder 7)
      Letters from Hallmark, NBC, and Foote, Cone & Belding.
    - Eagle in a Cage--Production and format., ca. 25 items. (Box 20, Folder 8)
      Assorted printed materials, including publicity clippings.
    - Eagle in a Cage--Script., 1 item. (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Elizabeth the Queen--Correspondence., ca. 25 items. (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Elizabeth the Queen--Production and format., ca. 25 items. (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Elizabeth the Queen--Publicity., ca. 25 items. (Box 21, Folder 3)
      Playbill, press releases, clippings, and assorted printed materials.
    - Elizabeth the Queen--Script., 1 item. (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - The Fantasticks--Clippings., ca. 20 items. (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - The Fantasticks--Correspondence., ca. 25 items. (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - The Fantasticks--Legal file., 19 items. (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - The Fantasticks--Orchestra scores., 36 items. (Box 22)
      Scenes 1-33 (missing 14 and 17).